What?
You're gonna marry
him?
Keep your voice down.
Do you want everyone to know we lost the goods?
But you can't marry him!
Yeah, My Lady.
We can just take the loss.
I thought about it.
It's just a formality.
The important thing is not to tarnish the agency's reputation.
You go to the courier station first.
I'll meet you when I get out.
Boss, don't fall into his trap.
In case he is so hungry that
he forces you to...
He?
I can beat two of them with one punch.
Right.
We should be worried about the boss.
Forcing...
Boss,
I have a bold idea.
Do you want to hear it?
No.
Then I'll say it.
You're recruiting a son-in-law anyway.
Why don't you...
I'm recruiting a son-in-law,
not snatching a bride.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll ask my brother to make a cover
to seal your mouth.
Stick to the plan.
My dear.
Come on,
let's have a drink together.
Congratulations to Lord Cheng and Madam Cheng.
Congratulations.
Our Cheng family has been generals for generations,
but now it seems to have ended with you.
Ah.
Here we go again.
A man should start a career after getting married.
If you had been learning martial arts,
I could have helped you a lot.
Don't look at me now.
I used to have
tens of thousands of soldiers
charging across the battlefield.
But now I'm stuck in this place,
and I can't even control my own son.
Ah...
Dad,
I'm already married.
As you wish.
What else do you want?
I don't want to argue with you on this day.
It's best for father and son to be kind to each other.
Come on, I'll toast to you.
This brat.
What's he up to?
He's very abnormal today.
My wife.
My dear wife.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My wife.
I'll teach you a lesson.
It's good to be young,
and have a good waist.
What are you talking about?
Ouch.
Oh, my wife,
are you okay?
Tell me,
what do you want to do?
Oh, Chief Su,
With your martial arts skills,
what can I do to you?
If I weren't so gentle,
you would've been killed by my fists.
Come on, my wife.
Get up.
Ah.
My wife,
you've had a long day.
It's getting late.
We should get some rest.
Let's go.
You're actually enjoying this?
You're not any better.
Alright,
they're already gone.
You've had a long day.
Get some rest.
Sorry about that.
I lost control of my strength.
It's fine, I'm used to it.
Can you give me the escort completion certificate now?
Ouch.
It still hurts a bit.
Do you think my arm is broken?
Stop acting.
My mission is completed.
Can I go now?
It's getting late.
It's really not safe for you to walk alone at night.
How about this?
I'll send you away after you serve tea to my parents tomorrow.
Don't push your luck.
I only agreed to the wedding ceremony.
The tea ceremony is another matter.
You have to go all out
to make it look real.
So many people saw me get married.
If the bride is missing the next day,
who do you think my family will blame?
You set me up on purpose, didn't you?
Stop.
Let me be honest with you.
I got married
just to leave Ning'an
and go to Yunjing.
As long as you help me finish this play today,
and take me away from here tomorrow,
I swear I'll never bother you again.
Besides, my parents don't know you.
They won't see you again.
How dare you treat
marriage as a joke?
It's all thanks to you
for posting a notice in Yunjing,
which reminded me.
You too.
Father,
how's the Nebula Assembly prep going?
I personally screened
every participant.
The Yun State has enjoyed peace for years.
If your business had a backing,
from the official
to the public,
Do you know what that means?
It means endless wealth.
So the winner of the Nebula Assembly
must be someone you can control.
Father, rest assured.
I will make sure everything is in order.
Good.
Go.
Yes.
Ah.
Miss Yan is indeed a fraud.
Hmph, I think you two are a good match.
A liar
and a fool.
Wait.
Tell me why you set me up.
Please be gentle, Chief Su.
I can't beat you.
Besides, think about it.
It's not your name on the marriage certificate.
How could I have lied to you?
Why did Meng Feifei write your name
on the marriage contract?
How can there be two groups
of people intercepting the escort?
How can you be so smart and be fooled by Miss Yan?
Wait.
Meng Feifei said I was your destiny.
Yes.
Meng Feifei is really something.
You haven't answered my question.
I'm in a hurry to get married
because I'm going to Nebula Assembly tomorrow.
If I don't have a wife,
I can't leave Ning'an.
I've only met Meng Feifei once.
She's too expensive.
So I didn't hire her.
And I met Miss Yan at the Matchmaker Pavilion.
She wants money, and I need her help.
Miss Su, I know you're a good person.
If you help me,
I'll owe you a favor from now on.
As long as I can afford to help,
I will definitely
do my best.
Well, you speak too fast.
I didn't hear it clearly.
In short,
please help me this time.
I...
Thank you.
You need to offer tea tomorrow morning.
Go to bed early.
You're not covering yourself.
Now that one more thing
has been taken care of,
why do you still look so worried?
I thought he was acting strange last night.
This marriage is so weird.
Don't worry about it.
Let the new daughter-in-law deal with him.
You two are always arguing.
New daughter-in-law?
I don't think she's sensible.
It's late,
and she hasn't served tea yet.
Don't worry.
I'll ask Yicheng
to check on her.
No need.
I'll go myself.
You are a girl.
How can you not even wear a hairpin?
Didn't your mother teach you?
I...
My mom...
Well,
as an escort,
you don't care about these details.
You don't need these.
But it's okay. I'll help you.
You can just let me take you away.
Why do you insist on serving tea?
I want to make my parents happy.
You're a good son.
If so,
why do you always look indifferent?
Do I?
Come on.
Just sip this.
Hmm.
That's enough.
You can tell my parents
that you want to go home.
And you have to take me with you
to Yunjing.
After arriving in Yunjing City,
we'll go our separate ways.
I...
Ah.
Everyone knows that
I'm marrying Miss Yan.
We are not husband and wife in name,
nor in reality.
The certificate proves you completed the escort.
and you have nothing to do with this.
It will protect your reputation.
It's very considerate of you.
But how will you explain it
to your parents?
Hehe.
Don't worry.
I'll make up an excuse.
Let's go.
Go.
Why do you escort in such a windy day?
Ah.
This young master wants to hire an escort.
I'm looking for a female escort.
Why?
You have a grudge against her?
Are you here to seek revenge?
I want to be an escort.
To be an escort for a woman?
You have no ambition.
Hey, hey.
Bro, let's talk this out.
Say it again.
She's out on a mission
and hasn't returned yet.
You want to be an escort?
I can hire you?
Haven't returned yet?
Could she have been hurt by those men in black?
Oh, no.
Hey.
Try running slower.
What were you doing just now?
And you, what were you doing?
Let's go.
Dressing like this again.
So uncomfortable.
Ah, ah.
Good moves.
Good strength.
Ouch.
Father, stop just panting.
Please enjoy the tea.
The tea served by my daughter-in-law must be good.
I just blow it a bit.
You, you kid.
Daughter-in-law,
you need to pay more attention to his studies in the future.
Yes.
I will take care of myself.
I won't let you worry.
How come this guy is like a different person?
He can say such things.
Good, as long as you two are in harmony.
Remember what I said.
And, my daughter-in-law,
if he does anything outrageous again,
just come to us.
We'll stand up for you.
Got it.
Dad, mom.
You're so quick to call us that.
Come on, get up.
You're such a good boy.
Now that you're here,
Master will be relieved.
Haha.
Our Cheng family
is a military aristocratic family,
guarding our home and country,
and defending a region.
But my son
has no martial arts skills.
He's a disgrace to our family.
You don't like writing,
and I don't like martial arts.
Why do you say that?
Good, you can talk back.
You're not that stupid.
I was just about to praise you,
but you're being stubborn again.
Enough.
It's a big day.
Why are you saying this?
He's married.
and has a wife to take care of him,
he'll be responsible.
That's for the future.
But for now, it's just between me and my wife.
Fortunately,
we have a capable daughter-in-law.
With you taking care of him,
I can rest easy.
That's the best.
Just have another
grandson who can fight.
I'll protect you.
You can focus on your studies.
Right?
Shouldn't we leave now?
Get to the point.
I know.
She's right.
I'm heading to Qiyong Academy in Yunjing City.
She mentioned homesickness last night,
so we'll leave soon.
Yes.
Well,
it's okay.
As long as you take care of him,
I'll feel relieved.
Remember, discipline him when necessary.
I won't feel sorry.
I know, Dad.
I'll teach him well.
We'll pack our luggage now.
Wait.
I disagree.
Mom, come on.
Last night,
she cried all night because she missed home.
I really feel sorry for her.
Please let me take her back.
Yes.
She just got here yesterday.
If you take her back today,
people will think we're rude.
This is not...
Betrothal gifts and wedding banquet.
We've spent almost all the money.
We haven't prepared the return visit gift yet.
Ah, mom, she is sensible.
She has prepared all these things.
So I feel more and more sorry for her.
My lord, since the child is willing to
do something decent,
how about letting them go back first?
Yeah.
My daughter-in-law,
when you arrive in Yunjing City,
if he gets into any trouble,
it's your business.
You can tie him up if necessary.
Dad, mom, don't worry.
He dares not.
Right?
My dear.
Yes.
Of course.
Humph.
Put them there.
Yes.
Grandpa,
why are you sitting in the draft?
You might catch a cold.
Let me take you back to the room.
Jiaojiao hasn't come back from Ning'an yet.
I'll wait for her.
Don't worry, it's a long way to Ning'an.
It's normal to be delayed.
Go back and have some tea.
Come on, lift it up.
Are you eating?
Hurry up.
Do you need escorts?
Master Su.
I'm Zhen Sanliang from the east of the city.
This is my son, Zhen Dabao.
I heard that Miss Su is graceful and beautiful.
So I brought my son to propose
to show my sincerity.
Oh.
I know the Second-in-Command.
You are the newly moved Bailiff Zhen
in the east of the city.
Yes, that's right.
My sister may not be as virtuous as you said.
You may have come in vain.
It doesn't matter.
The Second-in-Command has already told me
that we're here to arrange the marriage.
In that case,
Da Qi,
take them to the guest room.
Let's discuss it when Li Shi and Jiaojiao return.
Come, carry the luggage inside.
Dabao, let's go.
Your son
is quite adorable.
What does he do for a living?
Oh,
Dabao is two years older
than Miss Su.
His mother spoiled him.
He looks younger.
Our Zhen family
has farmland.
If Miss Su marries into our family,
she'll live a comfortable life.
Haha.
Dabao, perform a show for your brother-in-law and grandfather.
Let's go home. I miss mom.
Look at him. He's so homesick.
He will definitely
love his wife.
You're right.
So unique.
Hahaha.
My sister is hot-tempered
and plain-looking.
I'm afraid she's not good enough
for you.
Oh, don't worry.
I believe Miss Su
can take good care of my son.
It's not appropriate at home.
Yicheng, go!
Dig out all the money I hid.
All of it?
Yes.
Go now!
Okay, okay.
Why was your dad so ruthless?
He beat me without saying a word.
You're used to it.
That's my daily routine since childhood.
My father didn't expect that
although I can't learn martial arts,
I can dodge.
He can hardly hit me.
What a far-sighted man!
Your father must have seen that
you are a person
who deserves a beating.
Boss, who needs a beating?
We're coming.
Wow.
Boss.
You two wait a minute.
How did you get in?
Oh, Gong Xi, Fa Cai.
I don't have red envelopes.
They have been with me since childhood.
since they were little.
I see.
Let's talk about it on the way.
When Yicheng comes back,
we'll set off for Yunjing City.
Okay.
Pack up.
Boss, she
is not right.
She found herself a
live-in son-in-law.
Live-in son-in-law?
Butler,
here's the thing.
They asked me
if I have any sisters
who want to be their live-in son-in-law.
Ah?
They escorted me here for the wedding.
From Yunjing City?
Yes.
We are escorts.
We're here to check
if the escorted person is safe.
There are such rules?
Which agency?
I'll hire them next time.
Su's Escort Agency in Yunjing.
Escort?
What did you bring, butler?
My lady asked me to send some food
for you to eat on the road.
Young Master,
the guards have prepared the carriage.
You can set off at any time.
No need, these two escorts
happen to be going back to Yunjing City.
Let them take us.
It's cheaper.
Tell my father,
these
were arranged by the Young Madam.
Yes,
Young Madam.
Hehe.
Bailiff Zhen is right.
Jiaojiao
and Dabao
are a good match.
She'll be lucky for her.
Humph.
You came back just in time.
Zhen Yuanwai is here to propose a marriage.
How can I not be here?
Where's Jiaojiao?
She hasn't come back yet.
Did she go to fight again?
Li Shi,
you're back just in time.
You can talk more.
Da Qi,
help me back.
I'm not feeling well.
Dad.
I'll stay with them.
Don't worry.
Have a good rest.
What kind of person did you find?
If you have a daughter,
would you let her marry this guy?
He's matrilocal,
obedient,
and doesn't cause trouble.
How great!
The most important thing is that
he knows kong fu,
and he's good at it.
Oh.
If that's the case,
then it's not a big problem.
My Lord,
is he really not your son-in-law?
Nothing happened last night.
What do you think could happen?
Then why did you bring them back?
We are escorts.
He paid me, so I escorted him.
Is there any problem?
My lord,
I think
this Young Master Cheng is better than the others.
Why don't we just go with the flow
and take him back to the escort agency?
He does look pretty good.
Hey,
he's a scholar.
Why should I take him back to the escort agency?
To tell me stories?
Didn't you listen to him at the Cheng Mansion just now?
That was just an act.
Come on, let's go home.
Grandpa must be worried.
Actually,
he also pretended to get married.
What?
He just wanted to run away from home.
His father is the County Sheriff of Ning'an,
with excellent martial arts skills.
But he doesn't know any martial arts.
He is beaten by his father every day.
Ah.
Please wait in the carriage for a while.
We'll set off soon.
Chief Escort Su,
I have some urgent matters.
Can we go another day?
Just buying some specialties.
Won't take long.
Specialties?
You should've said so earlier.
I have some.
Ning'an is famous
for its elegance.
This is the most collectible specialty.
Perfect for gifts or personal use.
Are you trying to trick me?
How dare I?
I don't think you dare.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Young Master,
if Chief Su finds out it's just your poetry anthology,
will he leave us on the roadside?
What's wrong with my poetry anthology?
It's the only one in Ning'an.
How unique.
Get on the cart.
Are you sure you didn't find any blood?
She's really not injured.
Not injured.
Then where could she go?
Boss, look.
It's the escort team we robbed last time.
Let's go.
Okay.
Take a rest here.
Hey, what are you doing?
I should ask you.
We met bandits on this road.
If you appear like this again,
you may lose your life.
No way.
Are there really bandits here?
Chief Su,
next time,
let's talk it out.
Don't start with weapons.
You're the best at dodging.
Who can hurt you?
Besides, we'll go our separate ways
we'll go our separate ways.
There won't be a next time.
Chief Su,
if you ask me,
your acting skills are really impressive.
The way you cried out "mom" and "dad",
it sounded even more sincere than mine.
I'm sorry
for dragging you into this.
I haven't called out "mom" and "dad" for a long time.
This is for you.
Wait.
What's this?
It's your proof.
It shows that you didn't lose the escort,
and the marriage has nothing to do with you.
You finally did something right.
Let's just say goodbye.
I gave you the escort fee.
Chief Escort Su.
All right.
Since I promised to take you,
I won't leave you behind.
Besides the Nebula Assembly,
you also need to study at Qiyong Academy.
You've worked hard.
Is there a Qiyong Academy?
You grew up in Yunjing City.
You are
a liar.
Boss, why didn't we think of
robbing in the city?
Yunjing City is full of rich people.
It's much better than robbing in the wilderness.
Hahaha.
It's not convenient to rob in the city.
Then why do you go to the city?
To the Escort Agency.
Ah?
Robbery?
Boss Su,
I just want to know
if your niece will come back tonight.
What are you saying?
Are you cursing her?
The thing is,
I heard that the White Wolf robbed Ning'an yesterday.
The White Wolf is coming?
He is cruel and ruthless.
He killed people, robbed goods,
and raped women.
He has done all the bad things.
When he goes wild,
he won't even spare his brothers.
White Wolf is the escort agency's nemesis.
Su Yuejiao and the others haven't come back yet.
Did they really get robbed by White Wolf?
Well.
Congratulations to Boss Su.
For what?
If White Wolf meets her,
can she come back alive?
This escort agency won't be yours anymore.
No.
If she dies,
how can I get her huge dowry?
It's not a good deal.
She can't die.